Guide to the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 6 Records WAG.148
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 6 Records
1899-2000
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union. Local 6 (Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union) (New York, N.Y.)
Ward, Peter
WAG.148
68 Linear Feet in 67 record cartons and 1 oversize flat box
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions. Series VIII: Membership records were closed for thirty-five years after their creation and are now available.
Historical/Biographical Note
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 6 (now affiliated with the international union, UNITE/HERE) represents housekeeping staff, waiters, bartenders and other categories of service employees in hotel, private clubs and restaurants in the New York City area. The local grew substantially as a result of a major organizing drive in the mid-1930s, under Local president Michael J. Obermeier, and absorbed a number of smaller locals of hotel employees over the years. Significant gains came in 1938, with the signing of the first city-wide contract for hotel employees in many crafts and unions; the contract was negotiated by the newly formed umbrella group of hotel unions, the New York City Hotel Trades Council, headed by Jay Rubin. The HTC has continued to negotiate with the united employers (organized in the New York Hotel Association) on behalf of many categories of hotel employees. The Local is ethnically diverse, and has always included a high proportion of Latino workers.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains minutes, general subject files, and detailed records of each of the Local's divisions and departments (most of them arranged alphabetically by name of hotel, restaurant or club). The division/department records contain considerable information on organizing, membership at each location, grievances, and working life in general in New York's hotels, restaurants and private clubs. Also included are files of the editor of the Local's newspaper and membership applications (see series description below).
Series VIII: Membership Records, 1938-1961; 1975, contains applications filled out by hotel and club workers for membership in Local 6, and some dues records for club employees (1975). The membership applications record various categories of information, including place of birth; citizenship status; job, hotel or club worked at; length of employment, and place of residence. The applications were kept in binders organized chronologically by year (with some overlap between binders) and are not arranged alphabetically within years. Individual applications appear to be filed under the year of first applying, with additional date stamps added to the form in cases where the member reapplied after a break in employment. Individual item numbers (D series, H series, etc.) refer to an item on the form identified as "Ledger Page"; this may represent a cross-referencing system. The "Ledger Page" references have sometimes been crossed out and altered over time.
Box 51: The single box of records from 1975 consists of lists of members and their dues payments, grouped alphabetically by club name. Only a partial alphabet for this set (letters R through Y) was found in the collection. Note: this box contains restricted information and is available by special arrangement with archives staff only.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically.
The files are organized into nine series:
Missing Title
I: Minutes
II: General Files
III: Banquet Department
IV: Hotels
V: Club Department
VI: Restaurant Division
VII: Editor's Files
VIII: Membership Records
IX: Addendum, General Files
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 6 Photographs Collection. (Photographs #98).
New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council Records. (Wagner #123)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was given on deposit to the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives by the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 6 in 1997, under an agreement with Peter Ward, President of the Council. The accession number associated with this collection is 1950.263.
In 2001, HERE, Local 6 donated two mural panels, called the "Four Freedoms" by Hugo Gellert.
Rubin, Jay; Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union; New York Hotel Association; Obermeier, Michael J., 1892-; New York Hotel Trades Council; Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union. Local 6 (Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union) (New York, N.Y.); Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union. Local 6 (Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union) (New York, N.Y.); Ward, Peter
- Series I: Minutes, Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union. Local 6 (Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union) (New York, N.Y.)
  Labor unions -- Officials and employees.; Labor unions -- Organizing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Hotels |z New York (State) |z New York.; Restaurants -- New York (State) -- New York; Hotels |x Employees |z New York (State) |z New York.; Labor unions |z United States |x History |y 20th century.; New York Hotel Trades Council; New York Hotel Association; Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union. Local 6 (Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees Union) (New York, N.Y.); Rubin, Jay; Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, Jan-Jun 1942 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Local Joint Executive Board: Advisory Committee, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Executive Board, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Executive Board, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Executive Board, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Executive Board, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Executive Board, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Executive Board, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Executive Board, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Executive Board, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Executive Board, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Administrative Board, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Board, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Administrative Board, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Administrative Board, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Administrative Board, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Administrative Board, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Administrative Board, May 1905 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Administrative Board, May 1905 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Administrative Board, May 1905 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Administrative Board, May 1905 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Administrative Board, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Administrative Board, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Administrative Board, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Administrative Board, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Assembly Meeting, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Delegate Assembly Meeting, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Delegate Assembly Meeting, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Delegate Assembly Meeting, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Delegate Assembly Meeting, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Delegate Assembly Meeting, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Delegate Assembly Meeting, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Club Department Board Meeting, 1965-1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Dining Room Board Meeting, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - General Officers (Local 6), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - General Officers (Local 6), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - General Officers (Local 6), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Local 15: Executive Board, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1959 (Box 4a, Folder 1)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1960 (Box 4a, Folder 2)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1961 (Box 4a, Folder 3)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1962 (Box 4a, Folder 4)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1963 (Box 4a, Folder 5)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1964 (Box 4a, Folder 6)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1965 (Box 4a, Folder 7)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1966 (Box 4a, Folder 8)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1967 (Box 4a, Folder 9)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1968 (Box 4a, Folder 10)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1969 (Box 4a, Folder 11)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1970 (Box 4a, Folder 12)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1971 (Box 4a, Folder 13)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1972 (Box 4a, Folder 14)
  - Local 15: Membership Meeting, 1973 (Box 4a, Folder 15)
  - Local 16: Executive Board, Nov 1950-Aug 1952 (Box 4a, Folder 16)
  - Local 16: Executive Board, Sep 1952-Apr 1954 (Box 4a, Folder 17)
  - Local 164: Insurance Fund, 1953-1963 (Box 4a, Folder 18)
  - Trustees Meeting, 1982 (Box 4a, Folder 19)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Jan 1934-Sep 1936 (Box 4b, Folder 1)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Jan 1934-Sep 1936 (Box 4b, Folder 2)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Jan 1934-Sep 1936 (Box 4b, Folder 3)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Jan 1934-Sep 1936 (Box 4b, Folder 4)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Jan 1934-Sep 1936 (Box 4b, Folder 5)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Jan 1934-Sep 1936 (Box 4b, Folder 6)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Jan 1934-Sep 1936 (Box 4b, Folder 7)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Jan 1934-Sep 1936 (Box 4b, Folder 8)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Jan 1934-Sep 1936 (Box 4b, Folder 9)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Jan 1934-Sep 1936 (Box 4b, Folder 10)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Nov 1936-Sep 1937 (Box 4b, Folder 11)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Nov 1936-Sep 1937 (Box 4b, Folder 12)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Nov 1936-Sep 1937 (Box 4b, Folder 13)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Nov 1936-Sep 1937 (Box 4b, Folder 14)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Nov 1936-Sep 1937 (Box 4b, Folder 15)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Nov 1936-Sep 1937 (Box 4b, Folder 16)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Nov 1936-Sep 1937 (Box 4b, Folder 17)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Sep 1937-June 1938 (Box 4b, Folder 18)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Sep 1937-June 1938 (Box 4b, Folder 19)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Sep 1937-June 1938 (Box 4b, Folder 20)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Sep 1937-June 1938 (Box 4b, Folder 21)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Sep 1937-June 1938 (Box 4b, Folder 22)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Sep 1937-June 1938 (Box 4b, Folder 23)
  - Local 16 (Local 6): Executive Board Meetings, Sep 1937-June 1938 (Box 4b, Folder 24)
- Series II: General Files
  - Abramson, Sol, 1947-1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Administration: Report, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Affairs/Contributions, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Agreements: National, 1978-1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - American Hospitality Management, May-05 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Anniversary Banquet, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Anthony, Charles A., undated; 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Apprenticeship, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Apprenticeship Conference, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Assembly, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Assembly, May-05 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Audit Reports, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Barbados Workers Union, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Barbetta Restaurant, 1965-1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining, 1939-1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining: Club Dept., 1954-1960 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining: Restaurant Division, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Beefsteak Charlie's: Forest Hills, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Benefits: General, 1952-1959 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Benefits: General, 1968-1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Bentz, Betty: Clippings, 1945-1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bentz, Betty: Correspondence, 1953-1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bentz, Betty: Deposition re: Martin Cody, Lee Candea, et al., May-05 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bentz, Betty: Dues Books, 1941-1996 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Bentz, Betty: Examination re: John Stubin et al., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Bentz, Betty: General, 1967-1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Book Check, 1959-1961 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Britain: Hotel Industry, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Building Service Employees International Union (BSEIU), 1937-1940 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - BSEIU: Sullivan vs. McFetridge (I), 1945 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - BSEIU: Sullivan vs. McFetridge (II), 1945 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Burial Benefits, 1952-1982 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Business Agents, undated; 1982 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Business Meals Deduction, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - By-Laws, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - By-Laws, 1943-1950 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - By-Laws, 1974-1982 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - By-Laws: Amendments, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Canteen Food and Vending Service: Agreement, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Casino Gambling, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Caterers, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cerebral Palsy, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Certification Date, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chateau Madrid, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Chefs (Skychefs Company), 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Organizing, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Christmas: Expenses, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Christmas: General, undated; 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Party, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Christmas Party, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Clippings: General, 1950-1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - College Counseling, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Colombo Crime Family: Clippings, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Colored Hotel Employees of New York (CHENY), 1939 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Comite de Accion de Trabajdores Hispano-Americanos (CATHA), 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Committee for Political Education, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Committees, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Complaints from Hotels, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Computerization, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Concessions, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Conference of Offices and Delegates: Planning, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Consumer Health Agency Proposal: Rubin and Gluckman, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Contributions: Tickets, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Convention Center, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Convention Center Study: Arthur D. Little, Inc., undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Convention Reports, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Conventions, 1953, 1973-1979 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1954 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Jul 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Aug-Dec 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: AFL-CIO, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: HERE, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Members, undated; 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: President, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, undated; 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer (I), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer (II), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer (I), 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer (II), 1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Abadia-Alzapiedi, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Anderson-Ayala, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Bader-Bendesky, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Benetatos-Breitner, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Bremmer-Byre, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Cabrera-Churus, 1970- 1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Cippo-Cusick, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, DaCosta-Dempsey, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Denais-Duval, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Echaunen-Este, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Faber-Fecher, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Federico-Fulgraff, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Galanis-Gilmore, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Gionis-Gonzalez, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Gordon-Guzman, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Hackett-Hetherington, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Heyman-Hurley, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Ibbetson-Ivins, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Jaca-Kerbe, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Keriotis-Kyrargyros, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Lackas-Lee, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, LeGarrec-Lyons, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Mac Rae-Mazur, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Mazza-Montalvo, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Montes-Murry, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Myers-Nuniz, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer, Pabon-Partridge, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Cost of Living Adjustment, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Defense Fund, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Delegates Manuals, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Dental Fund, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Dental Fund, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Departments: Lists, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Discrimination in Hotel Industry, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - District Membership Meetings, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Districts, undated (Box 9, Folder 7a)
  - Doral Hotels and Resorts: Miami, FL, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Doral Hotels and Resorts: Miami, FL, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)